{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi7.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il prosciutto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427969.4676352,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ham\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "abbracciare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hug\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scary, fearful",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517253685.8522284,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"pauroso\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le orecchie",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427936.1645112,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ears\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "beverages",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le bevande\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "to listen to",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ascoltare\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "leg",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la gamba\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le onde",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517253692.4002535,
            "question": "Given the definition \"waves\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sea, sea-side",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il mare\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "very different",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427921.8563614,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"del tutto diverso\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "lo strillo",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"scream, shriek\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "lasciare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to leave, to let go\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "la gamba",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"leg\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "la crema per l'abbronzatura",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tanning lotion\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "pauroso",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"scary, fearful\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "contemporaneamente",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427958.3601587,
            "question": "Given the definition \"at the same time\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to walk",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"camminare\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "together",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"insieme\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "prommetere",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to promise\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "nuotare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to swim\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "to see",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"vedere\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "prepararsi",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get ready\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "da lontano",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"from afar\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "ham",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il prosciutto\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "vedere",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to see\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "to promise",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"prommetere\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "i denti",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"teeth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "ascoltare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to listen to\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "furbo",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cunning, clever\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "sunglasses",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gli occhiali da sole\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "amare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to love\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "ecco",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"here, there\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "del tutto diverso",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"very different\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "gli occhiali da sole",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sunglasses\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "il braccio",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"arm\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "subito",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"immediately, quickly\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "towel",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'asciugamano\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "tanning lotion",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la crema per l'abbronzatura\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "according to",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"secondo\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wash\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "avere paura",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be afraid\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to hear",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427943.32448,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sentire\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sembrare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to seem, appear\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "to watch, to look at",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"guardare\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "to wash",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lavare\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'asciugamano",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"towel\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "from afar",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"da lontano\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "camminare",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to walk\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "teeth",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i denti\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to leave, to let go",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489427555.949387,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lasciare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "berretto"
            ],
            "answer": "il berretto",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489427550.9173007,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cap\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scream, shriek",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489427903.6288905,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lo strillo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "muovere",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1489427712.3826559,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to move\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to fall",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427886.2887378,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cadere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to hold",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427537.5810163,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tenere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "immediately"
            ],
            "answer": "immediately, quickly",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427709.6667268,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"subito\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "waves",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427701.9072905,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le onde\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "arm",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427703.8589003,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il braccio\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to resemble"
            ],
            "answer": "to seem, appear",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427897.3688672,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sembrare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "affamato",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427786.0546594,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hungry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to close",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1489427782.0061016,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"chiudere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "secondo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427431.93435,
            "question": "Given the definition \"according to\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le bevande",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427673.9755275,
            "question": "Given the definition \"beverages\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "at the same time",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427869.5536413,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"contemporaneamente\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "some",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427614.4806063,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"alcuno\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "masticare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427424.7823315,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to chew\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ears",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427866.5461473,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le orecchie\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to prepare"
            ],
            "answer": "to get ready",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427422.4517925,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"prepararsi\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tenere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427757.6742902,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hold\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to greet",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427760.106474,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"salutare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to hug",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427879.2615068,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"abbracciare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il/la parente",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427612.4002042,
            "question": "Given the definition \"relative\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "innervosire"
            ],
            "answer": "innervosire(isc)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427495.3097196,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get nervous\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiudere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427427.014917,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to close\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "relative",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427507.5302403,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il/la parente\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get nervous",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427429.8387582,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"innervosire(isc)\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sentire",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427419.8823094,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hear\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cadere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427490.9975631,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to fall\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "salutare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427755.0586176,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to greet\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "insieme",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427763.2105925,
            "question": "Given the definition \"together\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il mare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427676.5518925,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sea, sea-side\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "riuscire",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1489427529.5970237,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to succeed\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scrivere",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427715.318943,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to write\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to chew",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427800.0337715,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"masticare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to move",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427736.255203,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"muovere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alcuno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427632.3876123,
            "question": "Given the definition \"some\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bag"
            ],
            "answer": "bag, pocketbook",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427627.240144,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la borsa\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to open",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427566.0568612,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"aprire\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to love",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427572.5526514,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"amare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to succeed",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427789.7418897,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"riuscire\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "guardare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427569.576958,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to watch, to look at\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hungry",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427912.5328138,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"affamato\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "here"
            ],
            "answer": "here, there",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427925.6965437,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ecco\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to swim",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427461.2662244,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nuotare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cap",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427575.6567652,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il berretto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "borsa"
            ],
            "answer": "la borsa",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427561.9691403,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bag, pocketbook\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sly"
            ],
            "answer": "cunning, clever",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427360.6430798,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"furbo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aprire",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427605.2456734,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to open\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be afraid",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427929.8484359,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere paura\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to write",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1489427364.195196,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scrivere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}